<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Academy_Lesson1</string>
    <string name="enter_your_text_here">Enter your text here</string>
    <string name="edit_prev_text">Entered text</string>
    <string name="email_btn">EMAIL</string>
    <string name="text_email_header">My opinion about app</string>
    <string name="my_mail_address">xxxx@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="enter_yore_message">Enter yore message</string>
    <string name="send_message_text_btn">SEND MESSAGE</string>
    <string name="big_info_about_me">I study on the android developer. There is an own project that is planned
        to be developed and someday to be poured on in GooglePlay.
        I am a fan of scrum, and I will fully share the values</string>
    <string name="company_info"> Analyst in some company</string>
    <string name="my_goal_text"> I want to be the android developer</string>
    <string name="love_sport_text"> I love sports</string>
    <string name="category_panda">Panda World</string>
    <string name="category_robots">Robot News</string>
    <string name="category_augmented_reality">Augmented reality</string>
    <string name="category_it_news">IT news</string>
    <string name="category_fun">Let\'s fun</string>
    <string name="preview_text_panda">During mating season, the solitary mammals bleat important information to each other through their dense bamboo habitat.</string>
    <string name="robots_obg_news"> Robots can now pick up any object after inspecting it</string>
    <string name="printer_obg_news"> Researchers develop 3D printed objects that can track and store how they are used</string>
    <string name="ar_obg_news"> Apple confirms it has acquired Spektral, a Danish computer vision startup, for augmented reality technology</string>

    <string name="full_text_panda">For solitary animals, giant pandas have an awful lot to say to one another.
        Their vocal repertoire comprises more than a dozen
     distinct grunts, barks and squeaks, most of which amount to some version of “leave me alone.”
        But when mating season rolls around, both male and female giant pandas turn to their preferred
        come-hithercall: a husky, rapid vibrato that’s commonly known as the bleat.
        The bleat not only alerts other pandas to the presence of an available mate, it contains important
        information about the vocalist’s size and identity.
        Given the dense bamboo thicket that limits visual contact in most panda habitats and the brevity of
        panda mating season — females ovulate just
        once a year and can conceive for only a few days — the pandas’ ability to perceive the bleat is critical
        to reproduction among this once-endangered species</string>

    <string name="robots_text_news"> Humans have long been masters of dexterity, a skill that can largely be
        credited to the help of our eyes. Robots, meanwhile, are still catching up.
        Certainly there’s been some progress: For decades, robots in controlled
        environments like assembly lines have been able to pick up the same object
        over and over again. More recently, breakthroughs in computer vision have
        enabled robots to make basic distinctions between objects. Even then, though,
        the systems don’t truly understand objects’ shapes, so there’s little the robots
        can do after a quick pick-up. In a new paper, researchers from MIT’s Computer
        Science and Artificial Intelligence Laboratory (CSAIL), say that they’ve made a
        key development in this area of work: a system that lets robots inspect random
        objects, and visually understand them enough to accomplish specific tasks without
        ever having seen them before.</string>

    <string name="printer_text_news"> Cheap and </string>

    <string name="ar_text_news"> On the heels of Apple  this morning inking a $600 million deal to acquire IP,
        talent and licenses from Dialog Semiconductor in Europe, it has also confirmed another acquisition of a
        smaller startup in the region.Apple has purchased Spektral, a computer vision company based out of
        Denmark that has worked on segmentation technology, a more efficient way to “cut out” figures from their
        backgrounds in digital images and videos, reportedly for over $30 million.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_item_news_activity">item_news_activity</string>
    <string name="news_btn">NEWS</string>
    <string name="my_card_btn">MY CARD</string>
    <string name="preview_btn">PREVIEW</string>
    <string name="thread_text_btn">Thread</string>
    <string name="error_its_no_data">Error: its no data</string>
    <string name="server_error_sth_bad_happened">Server error. Sth bad happened</string>
    <string name="real_nyt_news_btn">REAL NYT NEWS</string>
    <string name="dafault_topic_technology_text">Technology</string>
    <string name="choose_topic_text_title">Choose a topic</string>
    <string name="alert_cancel_btn">Cancel</string>
    <string name="real_news_btn">REAL NEWS</string>
    <string-array name="topic_array">TOPIC Array
        <item one="Technology" />
        <item one="Opinion" />
        <item one="National"/>
        <item one="Politics"/>
        <item one="Business"/>
        <item one="Science"/>
        <item one="Health"/>
    </string-array>
</resources>
