<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Academy_Lesson1</string>
    <string name="enter_your_text_here">Enter your text here</string>
    <string name="my_text">My text</string>
    <string name="email_btn">EMAIL</string>
    <string name="text_email_header">My opinion about app</string>
    <string name="my_mail_address">n.zales99@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="enter_yore_message">Enter yore message</string>
    <string name="send_message_text_btn">SEND MESSAGE</string>
    <string name="big_info_about_me">I study on the android developer. There is an own project that is planned
        to be developed and someday to be poured on in GooglePlay.
        I am a fan of scrum, and I will fully share the values</string>
    <string name="company_info"> Analyst in some company</string>
    <string name="my_goal_text"> I want to be the android developer</string>
    <string name="love_sport_text"> I love sports</string>
    <string name="category_panda">Panda World</string>
    <string name="category_robots">Robot News</string>
    <string name="category_augmented_reality">Augmented reality</string>
    <string name="category_fun">Let\'s fun</string>
    <string name="preview_text_panda">During mating season, the solitary mammals bleat important information to each other through their dense bamboo habitat.</string>
    <string name="full_text_panda">For solitary animals, giant pandas have an awful lot to say to one another. Their vocal repertoire comprises more than a dozen
     distinct grunts, barks and squeaks, most of which amount to some version of “leave me alone.”

        But when mating season rolls around, both male and female giant pandas turn to their preferred
        come-hithercall: a husky, rapid vibrato that’s commonly known as the bleat.
        The bleat not only alerts other pandas to the presence of an available mate, it contains important information about the vocalist’s size and identity.
        Given the dense bamboo thicket that limits visual contact in most panda habitats and the brevity of panda mating season — females ovulate just
        once a year and can conceive for only a few days — the pandas’ ability to perceive the bleat is critical to reproduction among this once-endangered species.

        Now, researchers have determined that the bleat works best as a local call. A panda can discern aspects of a caller’s identity. like its size, from a bleat within about
        65 feet, but the caller’s gender is only perceptible within about 33 feet, according to a study published Thursday in Scientific Reports.
        Megan Owen, a conservation ecologist at the San Diego Zoo Institute for Conservation Research and an author of the study, offered a human analogy for how this ability works.
        “If you’re walking into a crowded room and someone calls out your name, there’s a certain point where you can identify who that is, or maybe you can identify that it’s a male
        or female that is calling your name,” she said. “There’s information that’s encoded in that call, but that information degrades over distance.”
        [Like the Science Times page on Facebook. | Sign up for the Science Times newsletter.]
        To conduct the study, Dr. Owen and her colleagues — including Ben Charlton, another San Diego institute researcher who has studied panda bleats — obtained recordings of giant
        pandas from Chengdu, China, during breeding season. They then played those recordings through a speaker in a section of the San Diego Zoo Safari Park that contains bamboo similar
        in type and density to a typical panda habitat. By placing recording devices throughout the bamboo, the researchers were able to capture and analyze the bleats from various distances.EDITORS’ PICKS
        How Connected Is Your Community to Everywhere Else in America?
 </string>
    <string name="title_activity_item_news_activity">item_news_activity</string>
    <string name="news_btn">NEWS</string>
    <string name="my_card_btn">MY CARD</string>
    <string name="preview_btn">PREVIEW</string>


</resources>
